Jose Miguel Parami

+63 915-801-2505

josemiguel.parami@gmail.com

https://j-miggy.github.io/miggy.dev/

Oroquieta City, Misamis Occidental, 7207, Philippines

SUMMARY

Allocating time for me to acclimate to the workplace and its technology frameworks is a valuable investment. I'm a seasoned UI/UX designer and full-stack developer, skilled in crafting eye-catching and intuitive interfaces. My expertise bridges the gap between design concepts and coding, and I consistently adhere to agile development practices.

CORE SKILLS

TypeScript React, NextJS Framework Bubble.io
Javascript Angular Framework Firebase

NodeJS Ionic Framework

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TalentSift AI Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

Full-Stack Developer

- · Developed most of the features in their existing website in terms of UI, responsiveness, and usability
- Collaborated with the developers for ATS Connection with Merge.dev to Truto
- Developed all the requirements and descriptions with Notion

Raicom LLC July 2023 - Aug 2023

Full-Stack Developer

- Redesigned and organized their existing website user interface and backend structures
- Daily Stand-ups with an update/s
- Sprint planning to execution using Jira software

P&R Delivery Services

Oct 2021 - July 2023

Full-Stack Developer

- Planned and designed from scratch to wireframe & prototype in Figma
- Developed food delivery mobile application
- · Formulated most of the features based on client's requirements and descriptions

EDUCATION

La Salle University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2019 - 2023